Hello friends, welcome to a new
video, friends, in today's video
we are going to see how you will
get your airtelbank.com and if you like the video then do
like the video, so
let's start, friends, if you like it then
simply you have to tap on this option, on
tapping another option will appear in front of you,
two wheeler insurance, so simply you have to
tap on this option, on tapping
a QR code will open in front of you, so
now what you have to do is, friends, you have to
scan this QR code from another phone,
so whenever you scan this QR code,
a link will open in front of you, so
simply you have to open this link
and you have to complete the insurance work, so
first of all we will scan
this QR code, so
as you can see friends, we
scan this QR code,
a link has appeared in front of us, so now what we will do is
open this link, so let's open it,
after opening it,
such an interface will be shown in front of you, friends, so first of all
you will see here two wheeler
insurance ICICI Lant means  If the
insurance of IIIL company will be done
then simply you have to
fill the customer details here, first of all you have to
enter the full name of the customer here,
enter the mobile number of the customer, enter the email ID,
below that you have to enter the vehicle registration
number i.e. the number of the two wheeler
here and you have to
submit it here, on submitting the vehicle
details will be shown here, so you have to
match everything, after that you have to
tap on Get Kwid here, after tapping on Get Kwid,
such an interface will be shown in front of you,
here it will show you the first party plan, for
three years it will show you the
plan, for two years it will show you
and for one year it will show you the plan,
whichever plan you like, you can
select it here, but right now
friends, what we will do is we will book the third party policy here, so for this, first of all
you have to select the option of Third Party Policy Only
which is being shown here, on
selecting it, the
policy amount of the third party will be
shown in front of you, so as if
you click here  You can see that
you will have to pay Rs 843 for one year for third party
insurance, so you also got ₹1 commission from this,
friends, so simply what you have to do is
you have to tap on the continue option,
after tapping on the continue option, such an interface will be shown in front of you, then
you will get to see three options here,
PAN card, Aadhar card and Aadhar, so see
friends, here you have to
match the customer's details through PAN card, that is,
you have to do authentication, so you
can select PAN card here and if you
want to do it through Aadhar card, then
you have to select Aadhar card, so what
we will do now, friends, here we will
authenticate the customer through Aadhar card,
so simply we select Aadhar card here,
after selecting Aadhar card, you simply have to
enter the customer's Aadhar card number here, enter the customer's
full name, select the customer's gender
and select the customer's date of birth here,
after that you have to
tap on continue here, continue
After tapping on Pay, such an interface will be shown in front of you.
After entering all the information, if the
customer's authentication does not match here, then
you will see a message like this. So,
what you have to do here is simply
tap on OTP from here. As soon as you
tap on OTP, the OTP will be sent to the
mobile number linked with the customer's Aadhar card. So
you have to enter the OTP here and you have to verify it.
After the customer's authentication is complete, the customer's details will appear in front of you. You have to
match everything.
After that, you have to tap on Proceed here below.
After tapping on Proceed,
such an interface will appear in front of you. Here
you will see the customer's Fax details. You will
see the customer's previous policy details. So, simply you have to
scroll down here and
below you have to match the customer's details here.
You have to see everything here. After that, you have to
fill the customer's address here.  You have to
fill the nominee's details.
After filling the nominee's details, you simply have to
tap on continue here.
After tapping on continue, you will see the customer's
vehicle details, policy details and
personal details. So, you have to
match everything once. After that, you have to
add the terms and conditions here and
tap on continue.
After tapping on continue, the payment method will open in front of you.
You can also make payment here through debit card,
credit card, net banking and UPI app.
So friends, let's make 843 payment here.
After the payment is completed through UPI,
such an interface will be shown in front of you. Here you will
see the policy number and below you will
see the option of download policy copy. To download the policy also,
you simply have to tap here
and you have to download the policy and take it
out by printing it. So friends, in
this way you can make your
[Music]